Guide to the Varian, Inc. Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Varian, Inc. records
1950-2003
SC0889
Varian, Inc.
44 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
This collection was given to Stanford University, Special Collections by Varian Associates and Varian, Inc., in 1999, with additions in 2005 and 2006.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research; materials must be request at least 48 hours in advance of intended use.
Associated Materials
For additional records from Varian Associates (1948-1988), please see Stanford University Archives collection SC0345, Russell and Sigurd Varian Papers.
Historical Note
Varian, Inc. (known as Varian Associates from its founding until 1999) was one of California's first Silicon Valley companies. It was founded by Russell Varian, Sigurd Varian, and Edward Ginzton in 1948.
Scope and Contents note
Records include files on company history and anniversaries; press releases; photographs; annual reports and newsletters; manuals and other publications on products; and audio and video tapes.
Access Terms
Varian Associates; Electronic industries--California.
Collection Contents
- Records, Accession ARCH-1999-077
  - Photographs, Subseries 1
    Index to people in photographs in Box 2
    Ablu, Bob (?) Box 2, folder 18
    Abraham, Wayne Box 2, folder 21
    Acker, Arnold Box 2, folder 21
    Ames, Lorraine (?) Box 2, folder 21
    Andereggen, Henry Box 2, folder 18
    Anderson, Lenara Box 2, folder 4
    Anderson, Lenara Box 2, folder 6
    Andrews, Edna Box 2, folder 13
    Annual Shareholders Meeting 1952 Box 2, folder 15
    Annual stockholders meeting 1954 Box 2, folder 17
    Annual stockholders meeting 1956 Box 2, folder 17
    Asen, Bob Box 2, folder 8
    Ayers, Lorraine (?) Box 2, folder 19
    Back, Maj. Gen. George T. (w/Russ & Sig) Box 2, folder 17
    Baker, Andy Box 2, folder 18
    Ball, Henry Box 2, folder 21
    Banks, Millen (?) Box 2, folder 21
    Barne, Shirley (?) Box 2, folder 21
    Baseball game shots Box 2, folder 14
    Basketball game shots [most of folder] Box 2, folder 13
    Basketball team Box 2, folder 12
    Benham, Bob Box 2, folder 12
    Benham, Bob Box 2, folder 14
    Benham, Bob Box 2, folder 18
    Benham, Bob Box 2, folder 19
    Bernhardt, Harold Box 2, folder 18
    Bertram, John Box 2, folder 20
    Bisio, Marge Box 2, folder 4
    Board of Directors 1954 Box 2, folder 17
    Board of Directors meeting Box 2, folder 6
    Bock, Maj. Gen. George I. Box 2, folder 20
    Boniface Box 2, folder 5
    Bowden, Abbie Box 2, folder 13
    Bowling Committee Box 2, folder 4
    Brandin, Alf Box 2, folder 11
    Brennan, Ray Box 2, folder 11
    Brittain, Adaline Box 2, folder 18
    Brown, Bob Box 2, folder 18
    Brown, Jack Box 2, folder 18
    Brown, Mrs. Jack Box 2, folder 11
    Brunn, John Box 2, folder 21
    Brunner Box 2, folder 5
    Burger, Vernon Box 2, folder 10
    Cady, Nell (ID badge) Box 2, folder 6
    Cady, Nell Box 2, folder 6
    Caldwell, Dave Box 2, folder 8
    Call, Dutch Box 2, folder 4
    Calvin Box 2, folder 4
    Cameron, Emmet Box 2, folder 8
    Camurati, Dr. Enrico Box 2, folder 20
    Carlson, Bill Box 2, folder 13
    Carlson, Chispa ? Box 2, folder 13
    Carnahan, Chalm (?) Box 2, folder 19
    Carnahan, Vina Box 2, folder 19
    Carnahan, We (?) Box 2, folder 19
    Casgrave, Jack Box 2, folder 6
    Cau, Chet (5-year pin) Box 2, folder 17
    Caw, Chet (?) Box 2, folder 18
    Chan Box 2, folder 4
    Chan, Warren Box 2, folder 5
    Chodoraw, Nancy(?) Box 2, folder 10
    Chodorow, Marvin Box 2, folder 5
    Christmas party 1952 Box 2, folder 12
    Clark, John Box 2, folder 8
    Clark, Lewis F. Box 2, folder 17
    Clary, Al Box 2, folder 12
    Clements, Bob Box 2, folder 21
    Clements, Edna Box 2, folder 4
    Clements, Edna Box 2, folder 6
    Clements, Jane Box 2, folder 21
    Coleman, Jan Box 2, folder 9
    Cook, Maury Box 2, folder 20
    Cook, Velma (5-year pin) Box 2, folder 17
    Cook, Velma Box 2, folder 20
    Cooper, Ray Box 2, folder 18
    Couzino, Roy Box 2, folder 10
    Cowley, Lt. Col. Rex I. Box 2, folder 20
    Cox, Christina Box 2, folder 4
    Craig Box 2, folder 5
    Crossley, Al Box 2, folder 8
    Daniels, Harold Box 2, folder 18
    Daniels, Harold Box 2, folder 19
    Danow, Doug (?) Box 2, folder 18
    Darrow, Doug Box 2, folder 19
    Davies, John W. Box 2, folder 20
    Davies, Ken Box 2, folder 6
    De Stephano, Frances Box 2, folder 18
    Deal, Bob Box 2, folder 6
    Donovan, Jim Box 2, folder 17
    Dugas, Dr. Claud R. Box 2, folder 20
    Dunckel, Bob (5-year pin) Box 2, folder 17
    DuPrau, James Box 2, folder 9
    Dupre, Herb Box 2, folder 6
    Earls, Robby Box 2, folder 14
    Edberg Box 2, folder 4
    Edberg, Eric Box 2, folder 18
    Edberg, Eric Box 2, folder 5
    Fanos, Rose (?) Box 2, folder 18
    Farquard, Frances (?) Box 2, folder 20
    Farquhar, Francis Box 2, folder 15
    Farquhar, Francis Box 2, folder 9
    Farrell, Nora Box 2, folder 19
    Filmer, Jim Box 2, folder 18
    Fitzpatrick, Edna Box 2, folder 5
    flag raising ceremony Box 2, folder 10
    Flag raising ceremony Box 2, folder 11
    Fleming, Alice Box 2, folder 4
    Fleming, Alice Box 2, folder 5
    Flory, Al Box 2, folder 14
    Ford, Beth Box 2, folder 13
    Ford, Len (5-year pin) Box 2, folder 17
    Fowler, Harry Box 2, folder 18
    Franz, Pete Box 2, folder 19
    Franz, Pete Box 2, folder 4
    Franz, Pete Box 2, folder 6
    French Box 2, folder 5
    French, Gene Box 2, folder 8
    Frost, Kenneth A. F. Box 2, folder 20
    Gallis, Michael Box 2, folder 11
    Gandin, Paul C. Box 2, folder 20
    Gardner, Cliff Box 2, folder 10
    Gardner, Cliff Box 2, folder 17
    Gardner, Herb Box 2, folder 19
    Gardner, Herb Box 2, folder 20
    Garibaldi, Mary Box 2, folder 6
    Garson, Eta Box 2, folder 13
    Gaudin, Francois Box 2, folder 20
    Geisen Box 2, folder 5
    Gibson, Helen Box 2, folder 13
    Gilmore, Paul Box 2, folder 11
    Ginzton, Anne Box 2, folder 10
    Ginzton, Ed Box 2, folder 5
    Ginzton, Ed Box 2, folder 7
    Ginzton, Edward Box 2, folder 9
    Gordon, Ronnie Box 2, folder 21
    Grass, John Box 2, folder 6
    Grippe, L. Box 2, folder 17
    Hack, Olypia Box 2, folder 19
    Hackley, George Box 2, folder 20
    Hagseth, Roy (?) Box 2, folder 20
    Hall, Jack (w/Russ & Sig) Box 2, folder 17
    Hall, Jack Box 2, folder 13
    Hanley, Michael [child] Box 2, folder 13
    Hanni, Herman Box 2, folder 19
    Hanni, Herman Box 2, folder 20
    Harris, Harold Box 2, folder 8
    Harris, Johnny Box 2, folder 21
    Hartzner, Ira Box 2, folder 12
    Headrick, Larry Box 2, folder 6
    Heimbucher, Clifford Box 2, folder 9
    Hendrick, Virginia Box 2, folder 19
    Hendrickson, Leon Box 2, folder 4
    Henley, Earl Box 2, folder 4
    Henley, Earl Box 2, folder 6
    Hennies, Stu Box 2, folder 19
    Henry, Art Box 2, folder 12
    Hibberd, Robert G. Box 2, folder 20
    Hiestand, Norm (5-year pins for everyone until Stearns, Myrl) Box 2, folder 18
    Hiestand, Norm Box 2, folder 19
    Hildebrand, Lynn Box 2, folder 11
    Hildebrand, Phyllis Box 2, folder 11
    Hill, Charlie Box 2, folder 17
    Hill, Charlie Box 2, folder 21
    Hill, Charlie Box 2, folder 7
    Hodges, Eldred Box 2, folder 18
    Houston, J.D. Box 2, folder 19
    Huffnagle, Bernice Box 2, folder 5
    Hunter, Paul Box 2, folder 10
    Ingersoll, Jack Box 2, folder 8
    Jaynes, Ed Box 2, folder 18
    Jean, Frank Box 2, folder 20
    Jepsen, Bob Box 2, folder 15
    Johnson, Latte (?) Box 2, folder 21
    Judd, Charlie Box 2, folder 14
    Kane, Ralph W. Box 2, folder 20
    Kane, Ralph Box 2, folder 18
    Keithley, Jerry Box 2, folder 11
    Kelley, Bruce Box 2, folder 6
    Kelsey Box 2, folder 5
    Kelsey, Dan Box 2, folder 8
    Kestell, Don Box 2, folder 8
    Klein, Eva Box 2, folder 21
    Klevesahl, Carl (?) Box 2, folder 18
    Koeman, Myra Box 2, folder 21
    Koessler Box 2, folder 5
    La Mar, Helen Box 2, folder 17
    Lace, Bob Box 2, folder 8
    Laine, Jean Box 2, folder 19
    LaMar, Helen Box 2, folder 4
    LaMar, Helen Box 2, folder 5
    Laurencelle, A. E. Box 2, folder 20
    Laurin, Dr. Silvio E. Box 2, folder 20
    Lebizay, Jacques Box 2, folder 20
    Leger, Marie Box 2, folder 21
    Leonard, Dick Box 2, folder 15
    Leonard, Dick Box 2, folder 5
    Leonard, Richard Box 2, folder 10
    Leonard, Richard Box 2, folder 9
    Letenbaum, Sid Box 2, folder 9
    Levy, Leon Box 2, folder 8
    Lichtenstein, Milt Box 2, folder 8
    Lindal, Eve Box 2, folder 18
    Lise, Raphael (5-year pin) Box 2, folder 17
    Maguire, Nadine Box 2, folder 6
    Malling, Len Box 2, folder 21
    Management Advisory Board Box 2, folder 17
    Mann, Joe Box 2, folder 20
    Marsh, Charles Box 2, folder 10
    Marsh, Charles Box 2, folder 11
    Marsh, Charles Box 2, folder 18
    Marsh, Charlie Box 2, folder 17
    Marsh, Charlie Box 2, folder 7
    McAllister, Decker Box 2, folder 9
    McBride twins [children] Box 2, folder 13
    McBride, B. Box 2, folder 17
    McBride, Bill Box 2, folder 17
    McBride, Jr., Dr. William J. Box 2, folder 20
    McFadden, Gardon Box 2, folder 9
    McFadden, Gordon Box 2, folder 18
    McFarlane, Don Box 2, folder 18
    McFarlane, Don Box 2, folder 19
    Merner, Garfield Box 2, folder 9
    Messimer, Hal Box 2, folder 21
    Meuleau, Charles A. Box 2, folder 20
    Miller, Al Box 2, folder 11
    Miller, C. Box 2, folder 17
    Moffett, Peggy Box 2, folder 13
    Moreno, Dr. Theodore Box 2, folder 20
    Moreno, Lilly Box 2, folder 5
    Moreno, Ted Box 2, folder 15
    Moreno, Ted Box 2, folder 16
    Moreno, Theodore Box 2, folder 9
    Morgan Box 2, folder 5
    Morgan, Bob Box 2, folder 8
    Muffley, Dick Box 2, folder 18
    Murphy, Tim Box 2, folder 18
    Murphy, Tim Box 2, folder 19
    Musson-Genon, Dr. Rene P. Box 2, folder 20
    Myers, Bill Box 2, folder 18
    Nearing, Fred N. Box 2, folder 8
    Neely Box 2, folder 5
    Nelson, Bruce Box 2, folder 18
    Nelson, Bruce Box 2, folder 19
    Nelson, Dick Box 2, folder 19
    Nelson, Forest Box 2, folder 4
    Nelson, Forrest Box 2, folder 18
    Nelson, Forrest Box 2, folder 19
    Norman, Fred Box 2, folder 8
    O’Halloran Box 2, folder 5
    O’Halloran, John Box 2, folder 8
    Odell, Pete Box 2, folder 8
    Oeser, Hal (5-year pin) Box 2, folder 17
    Ostasink, Lou Box 2, folder 6
    Ostasink, Lu (?) Box 2, folder 21
    PA plant (no people id’d) Box 2, folder 22
    Packard, David Box 2, folder 10
    Packard, David Box 2, folder 9
    Packard, Dr. Martin Box 2, folder 20
    Packard, M. Box 2, folder 17
    Packard, Martin Box 2, folder 11
    Packard, Martin Box 2, folder 17
    Paquin, Phil Box 2, folder 17
    Passinetti, Frank Box 2, folder 13
    Perbam, Doug (?) Box 2, folder 20
    Perez, Mary Box 2, folder 21
    Perham, Doug Box 2, folder 4
    Perino, Mary Box 2, folder 17
    Perino, Mary Box 2, folder 9
    Peters, Ruth Box 2, folder 13
    Phillips, Larry Box 2, folder 12
    Phillips, Larry Box 2, folder 14
    Phipers, Fred Box 2, folder 10
    Pindroh, Johnny (?) Box 2, folder 21
    Pinkerton, Gerry Box 2, folder 13
    Point, Andre G. Box 2, folder 20
    Post, S. F. Box 2, folder 11
    Poucher, Rudy Box 2, folder 8
    Quintens, Helen Box 2, folder 4
    Ragano, Lucille (?) Box 2, folder 19
    Rayden, Virginia Box 2, folder 21
    Reighard, Paul Box 2, folder 4
    Renabarger, Peggy Box 2, folder 19
    Reyling, George Box 2, folder 12
    Rinebarger, Peggy Box 2, folder 21
    Robbiano, Paul Box 2, folder 14
    Robinson, Ivan Box 2, folder 8
    Rogers, Alice Box 2, folder 6
    Rogers, E. Box 2, folder 20
    Rogers, Emery Box 2, folder 11
    Rogers, Emery Box 2, folder 17
    Rogers, Emery Box 2, folder 19
    Rogers, Emery Box 2, folder 9
    Rogers, Omen (?) Box 2, folder 18
    Rork, Art Box 2, folder 14
    Ryerson, Rube Box 2, folder 8
    Saderquist, Sadey Box 2, folder 11
    Saderquist, Sadey Box 2, folder 17
    Salis, Fred Box 2, folder 10
    Salisbury, Esther Box 2, folder 5
    Salisbury, Fred Box 2, folder 5
    Sanford (of Tektronix) Box 2, folder 5
    Sarg, Lloyd Box 2, folder 21
    Sargent, Charlie Box 2, folder 8
    Saulages, Rolly Box 2, folder 17
    Saxon, Bill Box 2, folder 8
    SC plant (no people id’d) Box 2, folder 22
    Schiller, Hans Box 2, folder 11
    Schmidt, Bob Box 2, folder 14
    Schoder, Carl Box 2, folder 19
    Schultz, John Box 2, folder 19
    Schultz, Shirley Box 2, folder 18
    Schulz, John Box 2, folder 18
    Shaloayian, Harry (?) Box 2, folder 18
    Shareholders Meeting 12-4-51 Box 2, folder 7
    Shuffler, Bob Box 2, folder 8
    Shutts, Ham (?) Box 2, folder 19
    Sicklert, Lee Box 2, folder 13
    Sievers, Al Box 2, folder 9
    Silver, Harold Box 2, folder 11
    Silver, Harold Box 2, folder 17
    Simon, Dorothy Box 2, folder 13
    Smith Box 2, folder 4
    Smith, C. M., Jr. Box 2, folder 8
    Smith, Howard Box 2, folder 19
    Smith, S. Box 2, folder 17
    Smith, Snuffy Box 2, folder 4
    Snow, Don Box 2, folder 10
    Snow, Don Box 2, folder 5
    Soderstrom, Harry Box 2, folder 4
    Soderstrom, Harry Box 2, folder 5
    Sorg, Lloyd F. Box 2, folder 19
    Spencer, Bob Box 2, folder 6
    St. Clair, Maury Box 2, folder 18
    Stearm, Paul (?) Box 2, folder 19
    Stearns, H. Myrl Box 2, folder 20
    Stearns, Mryl Box 2, folder 9
    Stearns, Myrl (Admiral Award) Box 2, folder 18
    Stearns, Myrl Box 2, folder 10
    Stearns, Myrl Box 2, folder 15
    Stearns, Myrl Box 2, folder 16
    Stearns, Myrl Box 2, folder 19
    Stearns, Myrl Box 2, folder 21
    Stearns, Myrl Box 2, folder 5
    Stearns, Myrl Box 2, folder 7
    Stearns, Myrl Box 2, folder 8
    Stearns, Pamela Box 2, folder 10
    Sterling, Sy Box 2, folder 8
    Stoner, General Frank Box 2, folder 19
    Stoner, Maj. Gen. Frank E. Box 2, folder 20
    Stout, Rosemary Box 2, folder 13
    Sugimoto, Howie Box 2, folder 12
    Sukler, Lee & Lillian Box 2, folder 13
    Symons, Bob Box 2, folder 18
    Terman, Dean Box 2, folder 10
    Terman, Frederick Box 2, folder 7
    Thompson, Dr. Frederick C. Box 2, folder 20
    Tipping, Carl (?) Box 2, folder 18
    Trygstad, Burt Box 2, folder 6
    Unidentified lab workers Box 2, folder 15
    Van Erden, Paul Box 2, folder 12
    Van Erden, Paul Box 2, folder 14
    Vane, Art Box 2, folder 19
    Vane, Art Box 2, folder 20
    Varian picnic 1952 [most of folder] Box 2, folder 13
    Varian, Dorothy Box 2, folder 5
    Varian, Dr. Russell H. Box 2, folder 20
    Varian, George Box 2, folder 10
    Varian, R. Box 2, folder 19
    Varian, Russel Box 2, folder 18
    Varian, Russell [with others at meeting] Box 2, folder 5
    Varian, Russell Box 2, folder 10
    Varian, Russell Box 2, folder 11
    Varian, Russell Box 2, folder 15
    Varian, Russell Box 2, folder 21
    Varian, Russell Box 2, folder 5
    Varian, Russell Box 2, folder 7
    Varian, Russell Box 2, folder 8
    Varian, Russell Box 2, folder 9
    Varian, S. Box 2, folder 19
    Varian, Sigurd F. Box 2, folder 20
    Varian, Sigurd Box 2, folder 11
    Varian, Sigurd Box 2, folder 19
    Varian, Sigurd Box 2, folder 5
    Varian, Sigurd Box 2, folder 7
    Varian, Sigurd Box 2, folder 8
    Varian, Sigurd Box 2, folder 9
    Wachtel, Jim Box 2, folder 13
    Walker, Frederick M. Box 2, folder 20
    Walker, John (?) Box 2, folder 19
    Walker, John Box 2, folder 18
    Wallin, Walt Box 2, folder 8
    Wallwork, Marlin Box 2, folder 12
    Wallwork, Marlin Box 2, folder 14
    Wanake, Dorothy Box 2, folder 18
    Ward, Curt Box 2, folder 10
    Ward, Curt Box 2, folder 17
    Ward, Curt Box 2, folder 19
    Ward, Curt Box 2, folder 21
    Ward, Curt Box 2, folder 9
    Ward, Curtis Box 2, folder 18
    Wardell, Kay Box 2, folder 19
    Waterfall, Frank Box 2, folder 8
    Webb, Sid Box 2, folder 17
    Webb, Sid Box 2, folder 9
    Wert, Robert Box 2, folder 11
    Whitaker, Kate Box 2, folder 21
    White, Howard J. Box 2, folder 11
    Whitol, Arnold Box 2, folder 20
    Wihtol, Arnold Box 2, folder 11
    Wihtol, Arnold Box 2, folder 17
    Wihtol, Arnold Box 2, folder 9
    Wilkinson, Bill Box 2, folder 21
    Williams, Dave Box 2, folder 13
    Yateman, Will Box 2, folder 9
    Yeiser, Jack Box 2, folder 18
    Yewell, Tiny Box 2, folder 8
    Zijlstra, Paul Box 2, folder 20
    Zinser, Merle (?) Box 2, folder 19
    Zinser, Merle Box 2, folder 10
    Zinser, Merle Box 2, folder 17
    Zitelli, Lou Box 2, folder 18
    Zitelli, Lou Box 2, folder 19
    Zylka, John Box 2, folder 18
    - Magnetic Field (n-m-r) Photos (Box 1, Folder 1-5)
    - Klystron Photos: File 1 (Box 1, Folder 6-11)
    - Klystron Photos: File 2 (Box 1, Folder 12-15)
    - Facilities Photos: File 1 (Box 1, Folder 16-22)
    - Facilities Photos: File 2 (Box 1, Folder 23-28)
    - Facilities Photos: File 3 (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
    - People Photos: File 1 (Box 2, Folder 4-8)
    - People Photos: File 2 (Box 2, Folder 9-16)
    - People Photos: File 3 (Box 2, Folder 17-22)
    - Social Photos: File 1 (Box 2, Folder 23-24)
    - Social Photos: File 1 (Box 3, Folder 1-4)
    - Social Photos: File 2 (Box 3, Folder 5-13)
    - Varian and Bomac Catalogs (Box 3, Folder 14-16)
    - Aerial and matted photos (Box 4)
    - Album of portraits of members of board of directors (Box 5)
    - Album of portraits of members of board of directors (Box 6)
  - Prints, Slides, Transparencies, Photo ID Sheets, Subseries 2
    - Superconductivity Research, 1/90 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - X-Ray Tube Manufacturing, Eimac/Salt, Lake/Annual, 11/88 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Ximatron Component Testing, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Product - Turbo Pump; V-6- Turbopump for instal. In W.C. prod. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Statistical Process Control - Mfg., Eimac S.C./Annual, 11/89 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - X-Ray Tubes, Automated Testing, 11/88 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - X-Ray Tube Manufacturing, Salt Lake/Eimac/Annual, 11/89 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Clinac Manufacturing (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Linear Accelerator for Clinac, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Linatron 6000 X-Ray System Applic. at Morton Thiokol (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Linatron--A., X-Raying heavy casting (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Linatron - A., Cargo Screening/Contraband Detection (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - CT Scanner - APP, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Application: Advanced automated Sample Processor, Blue Diamond, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Ximatron Radiotherapy Simulator C-series, in-hospital, Prod. (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Simulator, Radiation - Prod., Ximatron, 10/87 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - X-Ray Tube (High-heat) (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Ximatron Radiotherapy Simulator - Prod., Cancer Therapy, 11/90 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Ximatron - Prod, Cancer therapy simulator (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - X-Ray Tube - Prod., 1987 A.R. (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - UV-VIS-NIR / CARY (Product) (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - VAC ELUT SPS24 w/ bond elut certify columns (product) (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - UV-VIS-NIR –Cary 4 and 5 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - UV-VIS Spectrophotometer - Cary 1 and 3 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - UV-VIS Spectrophotometer - P. 1987 Annual Report (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - 750 MHz NMR UNITYplus (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Turbopump - Macrotorr V-250 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Turbo Pumps/Vacuum Products, Turbo V-70 Macrotorr (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Turbo V-60 Turbomolecular Vacuum Pump and Controller (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Spectra AA-400 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Spectrometer AA - Prod, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Spectrometer AA - Prod, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - SPECTRAA 10/20 Plus (product) (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - SPECTRAA (product) (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Saturn II GC/MS (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Nuclear Magnetic Resonance Gemini NMR - Prod, 2/89 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Design and Manuf. NMR Unity Probe, Unity and Probe, 11/90 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - NMR Triple Resonance Probe (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - NMR -- P., Unity, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Nuclear Magnetic Resonance, VXR -- Prod., 1985 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Nuclear Magnetic Resonance, VXR -- Prod., 1986 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - NMR -- Product, Unity at U. of Wisconsin, 11/89 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - NMR Spectrometer (Unity plus 750 MH2) (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - ICP Mass Spectrometer, Ultramass (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Marathon Auto Sampler (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Vacuum Products - Minivac (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Liquid Chromatograph - Star LC (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Environmental Seminar, LC in Background, 1987 APP (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Hypothermia System for cancer therapy (research center), 9/85 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Clinac -- Multi-Leaf Collemater (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Clinac -- Prod., 1800 at Stanford, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Clinac 1800 at Stanford (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Clinac 1984 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Clinac Stereotactic 600SR, Stereotactic Radio Therapy (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Clinac R -- Prod, 2100C, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Clinacs (other than 1800, 2500, and 2500C) (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Clinac 2100C -- Prod., 1987 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Chromatograph, Liquid 9090 -- Prod (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Chromatograph, Gas -- P., Testing Beef/Australia (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - GC/MS - Saturn I (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Envirelut (Product) (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Helitest, Vacuum Products Torino, Contact: Luigi Dolcino (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - HPLC Isocratic Pump - Varian 9001 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - VVP055 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - ICP-OES (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Chromatograph, Gas - P., Gas Analyzer/Mobile Lab, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Chromatograph, Gas - Prod., Landfill Analyzer, Fall 1987 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - GC/MS Saturn 3, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Chromatograph, Gas - Prod, 3500 GC, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Chromatograph, Gas - Prod, High Temperature, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Chromatograph, Gas - Prod, 3400GC, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Sputtering/PVD System, 3290STQ Series (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Sputtering/Physical Vapor Deposition System, M2I Multichamber system (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Sputtering Source (Quantum source/Quantum cds) (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Sputtering System - P., XM-8, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Sputtering System - Prod, M2000 - Wafer Processing, 11/89 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Sputtering System - P., M-2000, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - MB2 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - MB2 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Sputtering System - Prod., M-2000, 12/88 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Sputtering System - P., XM-90 - Product only - Semicon, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Sputtering System - Prod., 3290, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Sputtering System - P., 3280/Semiconductor Production, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Sputtering System - Prod., 3290, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Sputtering System - Prod., M2000 (Shipment to Hyundai), 8/89 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Sputtering Source - Prod., "Love Source", 9/88 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Optical Power Converter - Varian Research Center (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - O.S. Multileaf Collinator (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Linatron (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Linatron 2000 linear accelerator, part of Cargoscan, 4/89 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Linacs, Historical (Stanford, Hansen) (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Chromatograph, Gas - APP, in lab, 11/89 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Clinac - P., Cancer Therapy - Mallinckrodt - '89 Annual, 11/89 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Mammography 1986 - APP (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Mammography - Applications, Senographe upgrade kit (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - NMR - A., VXR/AT Monsanto Research, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 3)